<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MENU on THE STAR INN</title>
    <link>/menu/</link>
    <description>Recent content in MENU on THE STAR INN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/menu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Christmas 2021 Menu</title>
      <link>/menu/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/menu/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Three hundred and forty-eight years, six months, and nineteen days ago to-day, the Parisians awoke to the sound of all the bells in the triple circuit of the city, the university, and the town ringing a full peal.
Star Inn Christmas Menu Starters: Spiced Pea &amp;amp; Ham hock soup with cheddar cheese sables.
Smoked black pudding croquettes with apple sauce.
Baked Camembert with crispy streaky bacon wrapped bread sticks.
Vegan garlic, lemon and chilli charred Brussels Sprouts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steakhouse Menu</title>
      <link>/menu/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/menu/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>Locally sourced meat of the finest provenance awaits in our expertly run restaurant in the heart of the Bridlington&amp;rsquo;s Old Town.
The Star Inn Steakhouse Menu STARTERS Stuffed Mushrooms | Chestnut mushrooms stuffed with dry cured bacon, shallots &amp;amp; cheddar cheese. | £4.50
Moules Marinieres | Fresh mussels in a traditional Normandy style- steamed in white wine and served with freshly baked buttered bread | £8.50
Soup du jour | Made fresh every day from all locally sourced ingredients | £4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wine Menu</title>
      <link>/menu/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/menu/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>Our wine list at The Star Inn is made up of wines which have been chosen to complement the cuisine of our Head Chef Lee Hayward.
WINE LIST RED WINE (Price per bottle) Rioja Santiago Tempranillo £14
Founded in 1870 in Haro, Rioja Santiago is the second oldest winery in La Rioja. One of only three wineries in the world that, due to its age, are permitted to use the word ‘Rioja’ on the label.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
