<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>THE STAR INN</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on THE STAR INN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Christmas 2021 Menu</title>
      <link>/menu/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/menu/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Our featured Christmas menu as we wind down 2021&amp;hellip;
 Star Inn Christmas Menu  STARTERS Spiced Pea &amp;amp; Ham hock soup with cheddar cheese sables.
Smoked black pudding croquettes with apple sauce.
Baked Camembert with crispy streaky bacon wrapped bread sticks.
Vegan garlic, lemon and chilli charred Brussels Sprouts.
Roast silverside beef and horseradish Yorkshire puddings.
MAIN Traditional Turkey breast, pork shoulder and crackling dinner served with:
 buttery potato mash &amp;amp; goose fat roasted Maris piper potatoes Lemon &amp;amp; walnut roasted Brussels Sprouts Braised, cider &amp;amp; apple red cabbage Steamed Broccoli Master Butchers best pork sausage and streaky bacon pigs in blankets Sausage meat sage &amp;amp; onion stuffing  Vegan, mouth watering butternut squash Wellington served with:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steakhouse Menu</title>
      <link>/menu/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/menu/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>Locally sourced meat of the finest provenance awaits in our expertly run restaurant in the heart of the Bridlington&amp;rsquo;s Old Town.
 The Star Inn Steakhouse Menu  STARTERS Stuffed Mushrooms | Chestnut mushrooms stuffed with dry cured bacon, shallots &amp;amp; cheddar cheese. | £4.50
Moules Marinieres | Fresh mussels in a traditional Normandy style- steamed in white wine and served with freshly baked buttered bread | £8.50
Soup du jour | Made fresh every day from all locally sourced ingredients | £4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wine Menu</title>
      <link>/menu/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/menu/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>Our wine list at The Star Inn is made up of wines which have been chosen to complement the cuisine of our Head Chef Lee Hayward.
 WINE LIST  RED WINE (Price per bottle) Rioja Santiago Tempranillo £14
Founded in 1870 in Haro, Rioja Santiago is the second oldest winery in La Rioja. One of only three wineries in the world that, due to its age, are permitted to use the word ‘Rioja’ on the label.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
